>> Jem Young: 让我们多聊聊 Nginx。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Let's talk
a bit more about Nginx.
关于 Nginx 是一个网络服务器一个逆向代理
About Nginx as being a web server,
a reverse proxy,
就像所有行业的千斤顶一样，真的，真的非常快。
kinda a jack of all trades, and
it's just really, really, really fast.
所以我想给你们看一些在内克斯做的事情
So I wanna show you some
common things to do in Nginx.
我们不会在关于内克斯的这一节里做太多的推文
We're not gonna do too much tweaking
in this particular section on Nginx.
但这些都是有用的。
But these are things
that are useful to know.
>> Jem Young: 重定向，实际上很强大，如果你今天来了，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The redirect, is really
powerful in fact, if you got here today,
你大概用了些重定向
you probably used some sort of redirects.
如果我想在我的网站上创建一个快捷方式，我可以说 jemyoung.com/something 和
If I wanna create a shortcut on my site,
I could say jemyoung.com/something and
我可以重定向到其他地方
I can redirect anywhere else.
因此，如果您想说我不知道，请在应用程序中输入 / 帮助路径。
So if you wanted to say I don't know,
put a /help path in your application.
其实不是你的申请
Actually, it wouldn't
even be your application,
这就在你的申请之前
this would be before your application.
所以你的申请是在，我们委托书是用这个斜杠来表达的。
So your application was at, we proxy
pass that to express with that slash.
但我们不能用它来表达我们可以在 Nginx 里做我们可以重做所有重定向
But instead of doing it in express we can
do it in Nginx, we can redo all redirects,
就像这样
things like that.
那是个特里维亚但我想你们一定会知道的
Then this is a trivia, but I'm assuming
some of you are gonna know it.
301 重定向与 302 重定向之间的差别是什么 ?
What is the difference between
a 301 redirect and a 302 redirect?
马克你有你的手我只是
Mark, you have your hand up,
I'm just gonna-
>> 标记: 永久重定向
&gt;&gt; Mark: Permanent redirect
和临时重定向。
versus temporary redirect.
>> 学生: 好的，那就 [INAUDIBLE] >> Jem Young: 是，
&gt;&gt; Student: Okay, then that's [INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes,
你要说的是这个吗
is that what you were gonna say?
>> 学生: 错了。
&gt;&gt; Student: That's wrong.
>> Jem Young: 这取决于，一个可以比另一个更好。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It depends,
one can be better than the other.
假设您的站点暂时关闭，并重定向您的状态页面，
Let's say your site is temporarily down
and you redirect your status page,
你想做个暂时性的重定向
you wanna do a temporary redirect there.
因为搜索引擎会搜寻，他们会说，这是暂时的。
Because the search engines will crawl,
and they'll say, this is temporary.
我们会在一两天或一小时后再回来，这并不重要。
We'll check back in a day or two, or
an hour, it doesn't really matter.
但如果你做永久的重定向他们会把它标记为
But if you do a permanent redirect,
they're gonna mark that as, okay, so
而不是去你的网站然后进入状态页面
instead of going to your site and
then the status page,
我们就直接把他们弄到状态页面上
we're just gonna get them
straight to the status page.
那么重定向，小心一点。
So redirects, be a little careful.
但作为 Web 开发者，我们应该知道可能存在不同的临时重定向
But as web developers, we should know
probably different a temporary redirect
在一个永久的重定向中。
in a in a permanent redirects.